3claws.com 2016-05-16

# Privacy Policy | 3Claws

##### **PRIVACY POLICY**

3Claws Inc. maintains this Privacy Statement (“Statement”) that summarizes our policies and processes for protecting the privacy of all personal information gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our website(s) or who download 3Claws Inc.’s products and services, and when and how such information is collected, used, and safeguarded. This Statement also explains how anyone can review, update, correct, or delete their personal information and specify what information, if any, they would like to receive from 3Claws Inc. on an on-going basis.

##### **Use by 3Claws Inc.**

We use the information you provide so that we may better understand the needs of our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. Specifically, we use your personal information for many purposes, including:

  * 1\. to allow you to register to use our products and services;
  * 2\. to ensure the continued smooth operation of our service;
  * 3\. to analyze user characteristics and usage patterns in order to better understand how our products and service are used and market them more effectively;
  * 4\. to communicate with you concerning your account or to send you newsletters, surveys, contest and sweepstake announcements, and information about our service or product offerings or the offerings of our business partners;
  * 5\. to prevent or investigate actual or suspected fraud, hacking, infringement, or other misconduct involving our products and services, or this Website;
  * 6\. to respond to inquiries, troubleshoot problems, investigate incidents, and handle complaints; and
  * 7\. to develop new products and services.

##### **Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our Statement, we will post those changes on our Statement page so you are aware of what personal information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our Website, and when and how such information is collected, used and safeguarded. You are responsible for periodically checking our Website for changes to this Statement. If at any time we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain e-mail consent from you. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your personal information in this different manner.
